Quick answers to quick questions!
Soteres One Grand Prix!
Quick question, Mr. Aya.
Please tell us about one piece.
A man gathers his friends and searches for his stomach!
It's late, and I'll wait until I've read the last one.
That's how you explain it.
Even though I said so.
But it's true, isn't it?
A man gathers his friends and searches for his stomach.
It's too late, last time.
The question is too difficult.
I don't know, I like flowers.
Then do it, Hana.
Okay, Hana-chan, let's go.
Tell us about One Piece.
An adventure story filled with dreams, hopes, and romance.
That's a little closer.
I don't know what you mean by an adventure story.
Does it mean a pirate king?
An adventure story?
I don't know if it's on the sea, in space, or where.
Is it on land?
Is the pirate part important?
It's a romance, so it's One Piece, right?
It would be easier to understand if Ruby entrusted her friends to you and became the pirate king.
It's easy to understand, isn't it?
That's my easy to understand.
But you know what?
Seino,Seino,
Okay, Moeka-chan.
Suzuki Moeka's cute parts.
Her cheeks, her smile, her presence, her gesture, her sweetness, everything.
It wasn't enough to call it a book of meaning,
Well, well, well, sure.
But it was easy to understand.
It was easy to understand.
It was Moeka.
Then, what I respect about Airi La.
I'll go.
You've got to be kidding me.
Dance pattern.
I'll see you later.
Later. Sorry.
You're late. You're late.
I couldn't finish my head.
I'm just coming out so much.
I guess I don't have that much respect for you.
Sorry.
Why the over-writing style?
You don't need it in your writing.
Really?
I over-wrote everything.
I was going to say, "Moeka, you've done a great job,
But it's too much.
I wanted it to be just a few sentences.
I thought it was too much.
It had to be at least an over-write. It has to be at least over-written.
We are entertainers, aren't we?
Just in case.
Even so.
We are entertainers.
You have to answer questions on the spur of the moment,
You have to answer accurately and concisely.
That's important.
I'm doing this project to improve my expectations,
This project came about in order to improve them.
I see.
This is the SOCLES 1 Grand Prix.
That's what it is.
Yes, I see.
The theme of this year's SOCLES 1 Grand Prix is,
Storytelling.
I see.
For example, let's say you are given the theme "Momotaro.
Immediately upon receiving the theme, please explain the story within 3 seconds.
Three seconds?
You have to be very quick-witted.
That's what I mean.
You mean you can't chew even once, right?
You have three seconds.
If you can speak in 1 second even if you chew for 2 seconds.
Four people like this, four ampompous people.
Ampontan?
Mentenan? Mentenan?
Ampontan.
Or puntinkan.
I say "ampontan," but I don't say it very often.
It's old-fashioned.
I'll do it.
You're really determined, aren't you?
That's great. You're the main one, though, aren't you?
Let's do our best.
Let me do my best.
Pretty for you At least with honor
In my life I want to make it happen with you.
Girl
I'm a girl of mine
Hear me now No meaning
If it's a word, I don't need it anymore
It's a now, it's a vow
You and me
Let's start the instant response one-group list!
Yeah!
I'm ready for anything.
Yeah, let's go!
This way!
Well then!
Ahhh, Anpanman!
I don't know!
I don't get it!
Wait a minute, wait a minute, wait a minute.
I just read it.
That's probably it.That's probably it.
Let me try again.
I can do the dormitory grounds sanitation.
That wasn't three seconds.
Wait, wait, wait.
That was one second.
That was definitely not a second.
That's a little fast.
It was one, two...
It was three seconds.
That's a beep!
That was a beep!
It's a West Como.
That's right.
If this is the center, it's a bit...
Our group will be in trouble.
It'll cause a lot of damage.
It's coming this way too.
One more time?
Please.
We have time to think.
You sure you want me to write the red one?
I see the theme. You know what it is.
You know what it is.
So figure it out.
Three seconds.
Let's do it.
Here's the theme.
Anpanman, the living hero, saves everyone.
Oh!Ooh.
That's good.
So that's what I'm talking about.
I have to get this out in one shot.
I can't do it.
I'll do it next time.
I'm still the MC for Ame-hura.
I want to show that I can think a little.
I'd like to show them that I'm a little bit smart.
I'd like to see that.
So you're in charge of Amefura's brain?
Brain.
A little bit.
I'm in charge of the brain.
A little bit of a brain.
In charge of the brain.
Okay, then.
Anpanman's
I'm in charge of brains.
Okay, let's see what you've got.
This way, please.
A boy in a school with a big hair
A boy.
A boy
A girl.
Boy
But not good.
It's not good.That's not good.
It's a story about the girl's character.
It's a story.
Now, that was a character trait.
The girl with the big hair.
There'll be a boy in the story, too.
I see.
I'm in charge of the backstory.
When the two of you were working on it, you seemed like you could handle it.
They seemed pretty confident.
That's why I'm trying to reflect on the fact that I can't do it this early.
I'm going to reflect on that.
I'm not trying to show you.
I'm trying to reflect on it.
I'm putting a lot of pressure on you.
I'm putting my hands all over you.
Okay.
Here we go.
I don't know, Ghibli.
The cat...
I've never seen Totoro.
A cat.
Cats.
Only cats.
Cat.
Cat bus
I told you Ghibli can't do it.
I've seen it.
It's some kind of English version.Why does it look like the English version?
Why does it look like the English version?
I'm in love with this one.
Well, Moeka is itching for some more
I've got a problem for Moeka.
What is it?
I've changed my mind about this project...
Here we go.
This way, please.
It's light blue.
What is it?
It's terrible.
Light blue.
A cat.
Light blue something
It's out of the question when you go to
Cats are hard to come by.
Cat-shaped robot
Yes, it is.
I'm glad you liked it.
I get itchy sometimes.
That's enough.
But...
I don't want to tell you.
I'd like to give you a proper answer.
Well, if that's the case...
I'll get that cartoon.
I'd like to go as far as that.
Right this way.
We're good friends.We're so close.
Making, singing and dancing
Mass games
Thank you for your hard work
Thank you very much for your hard work.
You could have done it, couldn't you?